Guide to the W.S.U. Lantern Slides 1892-1944
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
W.S.U. Lantern Slides
1892-1944
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
PC 6
Washington State University Libraries: Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
7 containers. 3.5 linear feet of shelf space. 690 items.
Lantern slides were used for instructional and promotional purposes at WSU early in the century.
Lantern slides were used for instructional and promotional purposes at WSU early in the century.
The collection is organized into eight series: Buildings, Faculty, Students, Sports, Campus Events, Pullman Scenes, Landscapes, and Teaching Aids.
This collection is open for research use.
The bulk of the WSU lantern slides were donated to the Washington State University Library by Dr. Al Butler. The donors of the rest of the collection are not accounted for.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University--Buildings; Washington State University--History; Historical Photograph Collections. waps
Historic buildings--Washington (State)--Pullman; Universities and colleges--Washington (State)--History
Colleges and Universities; Photographs; Washington (State); Architecture
Lantern slides -- Washington (State)--Pullman--1892-1944. gmgpc waps
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Series 1: Buildings
  - Proposed Administration Building, 1890-1894 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administration Building and Cabbage Patch, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administration Building, 1893; Negative 87-502 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration Building, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration Building, 1906-1907; Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Down Walkway from Administration Building, 1907; Negative 87-506 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administration Building, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administration Building, 1908; Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administration Building, 1910-1911 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administration Building, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Administration Building, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Long Walk Administration Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Administration Building and Gateway, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Washington State College Archway - Maiden Ln., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Washington State College Archway, Maiden Ln., undated; Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Washington State College Archway - Maiden Ln., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Washington State College Archway - Maiden Ln., undated; Negative 87-508 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station. "A view of the (farms) and experimental fields of wheat. To the left are spring grains; to the right fall grains.", 1906 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, 1920; Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bryan Hall, 1908-1944; Cracked (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bryan Hall, 1908-1944; Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bryan Hall Clock Tower, 1908-1944 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Painting Bryan Hall Clock Tower; Sigma Tau Fraternity, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bryan Hall Clock Tower, undated; Cracked. Negative 87-511 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Carpenter Hall, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Carpenter Hall, 1915; Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Carpenter Hall, 1920-1922; Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - College Hall, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - College Hall, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Crib - W.A.C. first classroom building, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Creamery, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Creamery, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Old Ferry and College Halls, 1892-1897 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Old Ferry Hall, 1892-1897 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Old Ferry Hall, 1892-1897 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Old Ferry Hall, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Ferry Hall, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Ferry Hall, 1912-1913; Negative 3201-14. Color tinted (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Gymnasium, 1892-1910 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Old Gymnasium, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Old Gymnasium, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Sketch: Proposed Gymnasium for W.S.C., undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Sketch: Gymnasium Longitudinal section, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Sketch: Gymnasium Basement Floor Plan, undated; Broken (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Sketch: Gymnasium Mezzanine Floor Plan, undated; Cracked (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Sketch: Gymnasium Main Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Sketch: Gymnasium Second Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Sketch: Gymnasium Balcony and Bleachers Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Gymnasium Construction, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Sketch: Proposed Women's Gymnasium, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Sketch: Women's Gymnasium Basement Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Sketch: Women's Gymnasium Ground Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Sketch: Women's Gymnasium First Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Sketch: Women's Gymnasium Second Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Sketch: Women's Gymnasium Third Floor Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Old Library in Administration Building, 1892-1909 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Old Library in Bryan Hall, 1909-1944 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Mechanical Building, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Mechanical and Mining Building, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Old Mining Building, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Old Engineering/Mechanical Building, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Engineering Drawing Class - Mechanical Arts Building, 1892-1910 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Electric Lab - Mechanical Building, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Agriculture/Engineering, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Architectural Engineering Class - Mechanical Arts Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Classroom with surveyor equipment - Mechanical Arts Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Factory Interior - Mechanical Arts Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Frame Drilling Machine - Locomotive Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - McCroskey Hall, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - McCroskey Hall, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Winter Landscape - McCroskey and Stevens Halls, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Morrill Hall, 1905; Broken. With duplicate negative (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Morrill Hall and Mechanical Building Carpenter Shop, 1908; Color tinted (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Morrill Hall, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Morrill Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Morrill and Ferry Halls, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Music Conservatory, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Music Conservatory, 1906; Cracked (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Music Conservatory, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Music Conservatory, 1910-1944 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Sketch: North-South (Wilmer-Davis) Hall Basement Floor Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Sketch: North-South Hall Ground Floor Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Sketch: North-South Hall First Floor Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Sketch: North-South Hall Second Floor Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Sketch: North-South Hall Third Floor Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Sketch: North-South Hall Fourth Floor Plan, undated; Broken (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Power Plant, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - President's House, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Rogers Field - The Serpentine, 1910; Cracked (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Rogers Field, 1910; Negative 89-182 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Rogers Field, 1892-1920; Cracked. Color tinted (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Construction of Rogers Field Grandstand, 1920-1924; Negative 89-183 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Animal Exhibit Museum - Science Hall, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Science Hall, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Old Science Hall - East Side, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Science Hall, 1921; Negative 89-032 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Science Building, snow scene, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Department of Botany Laboratory Classroom - Science Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Biology/Botany Classroom - Science Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Biology/Botany Classroom - Science Hall, undated; Negative 89-037 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Biology/Botany Classroom - Science Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Biology Class - Science Hall, undated; Negative 87-515 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Entomology Class, undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Dr. Shaw, Zoology Class, Science Hall, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Laboratory - Science Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Laboratory - Science Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Laboratory Classroom - Science Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Laboratory Classroom - Science Hall, undated; Negative 87-513 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Campus Scene early spring - Silver Lake and Bryan Hall, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Silver Lake, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Silver Lake, undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Silver Lake Bridge, undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Silver Lake Bridge, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Silver Lake Bridge, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Silver Lake Bridge, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Silver Lake reflections, undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Stevens Hall, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Stevens Hall, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Stevens Hall, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Stevens Hall, 1910-1911 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Stimson Hall, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Hay Stove, Domestic Sciences Department (Home Economics) - Van Doren Hall, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 133a)
  - Construction of Van Doren Hall, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 133b)
  - Van Doren Hall Classroom, undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Van Doren Hall Kitchen, undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Veterinary School Laboratory. Horse surgery, undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Veterinary Sciences Lab, undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Wilson Hall, 1912; Cracked (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Beta Theta Pi House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Kappa Delta House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Kappa Delta House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Pi Beta Phi House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Phi Kappa Tau House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Sigma Chi House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Sigma Kappa House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Sigma Nu House, 1925; Broken (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon House, 1925; Cracked (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Theta Chi House, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Proposed Library, west elevation, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Proposed Library, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Proposed Library, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Proposed Library Cross-Section, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Proposed Library Basement Floor Plan, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Proposed Library Ground Floor Plan, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Proposed Library Main Floor Plan, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Proposed Library Second Floor Plan, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Proposed Library Third Floor Plan, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Proposed Apartments for Married Students, 1940-1959 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Proposed Classroom Building - Todd Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Proposed Memorial Student Building, undated (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Early Campus Scene, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Washington State College Campus, 1893; Cracked (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Washington State College Campus, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Early View of Campus, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - W.S.C. Campus, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - W.S.C. Campus, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - W.S.C. Campus, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - W.S.C. Campus, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Early W.S.C. Campus Photograph, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Early W.S.C. Campus Scene, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Early W.S.C. Campus Scene, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - W.S.C. Campus Scene, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - W.S.C. Campus Scene, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - W.S.C. Campus Scene, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - W.S.C. Campus Scene from South, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - W.S.C. Campus Scene, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - W.S.C. Campus Scene, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - W.S.C. Campus in Winter, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - W.S.C. Campus in Winter, 1920-1929; Negative 87-509 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - W.S.C. Campus in Winter, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - W.S.C. Campus in Winter, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - W.S.C. Campus in Winter, undated (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - W.S.C. Campus in Winter, undated (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - W.S.C. in Winter, undated (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Campus Scene, undated (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - W.S.C. Campus Scene, undated (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - W.S.C. North View of Campus, undated (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Sketch of Campus, undated (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Sketch of Campus, undated (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Aerial photo of Campus, undated (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Early Photograph of Campus, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Construction of Morrill Hall, undated (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Art Classroom, Unknown Building, 1904; Cracked (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Dr. F.C. Chalfant - Department of Modern Language - Language Lab - Unknown Building, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Chalfant Language Lab - Unknown Building, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Bakery, undated (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Classroom, undated (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Dining Hall, undated (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Laboratory, undated (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Drawing Classroom, undated (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Classroom, undated (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Three women in Laboratory, undated (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Dining Hall, undated (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Storage Room, undated (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Three Wooden Vats, undated (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Model House - Pullman, WA, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Old University Building - University of Washington, undated (Box 3, Folder 212)
- Series 2: Faculty
  - Dr. Bohler - Physical Ed. and Athletics, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Dr. Bryan - Age 37 when he took charge of W.S.C., 1905 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Dr. Bryan welcoming Senator McCroskey, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - H.V. Carpenter - Engineering Department, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Dr. Cleveland - Department of Psychology and Education, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Dean Fulmer - Chemistry, 1892-1900; Negative 87-500 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Professor Melander and Zoology - Science Hall, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Professor Morris - Horticulture, 1910-1911 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Dr. Shaw - Zoology, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Nancy Van Doren - Department of Domestic Sciences - Home Ec., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Dean Wegner - Veterinary Sciences, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Faculty Football Team - Dr. Bryan holding football (edited image), 1902 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Faculty in front of Science Hall, 1904; Negative 89-034 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Faculty group - Dr. Piper standing left, Dr. Bryan standing right, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Faculty group - Dr. Piper standing left, Dr. Bryan standing right, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Music Department - Professor Strong standing right, 1909-1910 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Commissioned officers and staff - W.S.C. Military, 1900. (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Commanding officers - W.S.C. Military, 1909-1910 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Dr. Shaw and class, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Regents (from right to left) - President Holland, Duncan Dunn, Wilmer, Davis, Hulbert, Ritz, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - President's Mansion, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Claudius O. Johnson Residence - Chair Department of History and Political Science, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Harry C. Weller Residence - Asst. Professor Architecture, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Dr. Bryan's Desk, 1908; Cracked (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Dr. Bryan's Desk, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Living Room of Practice Cottage - Nancy Van Doren, Preceptress, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Three men - Thomas Edison, George Eastman, and ?, undated (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Women and children on house porch, undated (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Domestic Interior, undated (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Group Portrait, undated (Box 3, Folder 242)
- Series 3: Students
  - Military Students and Cannon, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Student Military Maneuvers, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Student Military, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Student Military Maneuvers, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Class of, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Glee and Mandolin Clubs, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Graduating Class, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Graduating Class, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Men sitting on Bridge - Silver Lake, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Students in Dormitory, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Student's Dorm Room, 1892-1905 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Military Class Portrait, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Military Students Eating, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Military Ball, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Lake de Puddle (Silver Lake), 1908 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Lake de Puddle (Silver Lake) - Biology Class, 1908; Negative 87-501 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Military Students, 1908; Negative 87-505 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Spokane Military Encampment, NW Blvd., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Lake de Puddle, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Graduating Class, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Band Practicing behind Bryan Hall, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Traditional Senior Bench, 1922; Negative 87-503 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Coasting Party - Lambda Chi Alpha Fraternity, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Freshman Class, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Women's Military, undated (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - Women's Military, undated (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Women's Military, undated (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Military Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - Drama Group, undated (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - Students in Costumes - Drama Group, undated (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - Group Portrait of Women, undated (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - Group Portrait of Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Graduating Student, undated (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Group Picture of Students, undated; Negative 89-033 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - Group of Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - Portrait of Young Man, undated (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Group Photograph, undated (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Man in Derby Hat, undated (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - People and Cows, undated (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Men in Orchard, undated (Box 4, Folder 282)
- Series 4: Sports
  - W.A.C. Athletic Entertainment, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - W.A.C. Athletic Entertainment, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - W.A.C. Athletic Entertainment, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Basketball Team, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Women's Basketball, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - W.A.C. Baseball, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Baseball Team, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Football Team, 1896; Negative 89-187 (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Football Team, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Championship Football Team, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Football Team, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Football Team - Practice, 1906; Negative 89-184 (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - Football Team, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Track Team, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Track Team, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Track Team, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - Track Team, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Track Meet, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Track Meet - 220 yd. Hurdles, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Track Meet - Rogers Field, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Track Meet - Osaka, Japan, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Track Meet, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Track Meet, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Track Meet, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Track Meet - NW Conference, 1920; Negative 89-181 (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Track Meet - 220 yd. Dash, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Track Meet - W.S.C. vs. O.A.C., 1922 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Track Meet - W.S.C., 1922 (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Track Meet. Runners Charles Paddock and Loren Murchison, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Track Meet, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Track Meet, runners starting race, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Track Meet, runners starting race, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Track Meet, runners at finish line, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Track Meet, runner at finish line, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Track Runner, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Track Team Member, 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - Track Team Member, undated (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Track Practice, undated (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Paris Intercollegiate Track Meet, undated (Box 4, Folder 334)
- Series 5: Campus Events
  - Campus Day, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Campus Day, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Campus Day, 1915; Color tinted (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Campus Day, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Campus Day, 1917; Color tinted (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Campus Day, bread line, Van Doren Hall, undated (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - Foundation Day, 1911; Negative 87-510 (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - Foundation Day - Miners Exhibit, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - Foundation Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - Foundation Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - Foundation Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - Foundation Day Parade, undated (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Foundation Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Foundation Day Parade, undated (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - Foundation Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Foundation Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Foundation Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - W.S.C. Display - W. Main Street, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - W.S.C. Float, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - Veterinary Sciences Display, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - Stock Show - Dairy Exhibit, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 365)
- Series 6: Pullman Scenes
  - Pullman, 1900; With duplicate negative (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - Pullman Military at Main and Grand intersection, 1905; Cracked (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - Pullman Farm, looking East of Rogers Field, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - Main Street in Pullman, 1911; With duplicate negative (Box 4, Folder 369)